http://www.contestyachts.com/privacy-policy

Motor Yachts
52MC Fastlane52MC Flybridge52MC Open Sport52MC Classic52MC T-top52MC Fastlane
Maarehaa Island
Orissaare Estland (Estonia)
Celebrating the sale of the 50th Contest 50CS
Almost here - only months to go!
Contest Yachts deliver first Contest 85CS – Polina Star IV
Game-changing new Contest 55CS
Open House @ Contest Yachts
World premiere Contest 55CS at boot Düsseldorf
New Contest 59CS!
NEWSFLASH… Contest 55CS wins best Bluewater Cruiser 2020!
BOOT Dusseldorf 2020
Open House Contest Yachts cancelled due to novel coronavirus
Ultramodern zeiljacht met karakter
Contest 67CS:
Login
Privacy policy Privacy statement Conyplex B.V.
IntroductionConyplex B.V. takes your privacy very seriously and shall handle your personal data with the utmost security and care. In this Privacy Statement you will learn how we handle your data as well as learn about your rights concerning our processing of your data. We advise that you read this Privacy Statement thoroughly. Should you have any questions or remarks, please contact us at privacy@contestyachts.com.Who is Conyplex B.V.?Conyplex B.V. (Ltd) is the private company Conyplex B.V., with registered office at (1671 GD) Medemblik listed at the Traderegister of the Dutch Chamber of Commerce under 36011996.Conyplex B.V. is as the controller ultimately responsible with regard to the processing of your personal data.
Conyplex B.V. has appointed a data protection officer. You may contact A. Pastor at privacy@contestyachts.com.
How does Conyplex B.V. use your personal data?Underneath you will find an overview of the purposes for the processing of your personal data. You will also find a specification of which data Conyplex B.V. uses for that specific purpose, the legal justification, and the amount of time Conyplex B.V. keeps this data. For clarity’s sake, we have categorised the purposes.Services, customer management and financial administrationPurpose:                      Financial administrationInformation:                Company name, Billing address, Bank details, Outstanding balanceLegal basis:                 Legal obligationStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      Order ManagementInformation:               Home address, Delivery address, Billing address, Email, Phone, Payment information, Account number, Order Number, Complaint content, COC number, VAT number, Customer numberLegal basis:                 Necessary for the performance of a contractStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      Handling complaintsInformation:                 Home address, Delivery address, Billing address, Email, Phone, Payment information, Account number, Order Number, Complaint content, COC number, VAT number, Customer numberLegal basis:                 Necessary for the performance of a contractStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      InvoicingInformation:                Home address, Delivery address, Billing address, Email, Phone, Payment information, Account number, Order Number, Complaint content, COC number, VAT number, Customer numberLegal basis:                 Necessary for the performance of a contractStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      CRMInformation:                 Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsImportance:                Commercial interestsStorage period:           As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      Job applicationInformation:                Name, Email, address, PhoneLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsImportance:                Commercial interestsStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
MarketingPurpose:                      Direct marketingInformation:                Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:      Commercial interestsStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                     NewsletterInformation:                Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:      Commercial interestsStorage period:           As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                     RetargetingInformation:               Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:     Commercial interestsStorage period:           As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      Social media marketingInformation:                Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:     Commercial interests|Storage period:           As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      Behavioural targetingInformation:                 Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:      Commercial interestsStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      Loyalty programInformation:                 Name, Home address, Email, Phone, Click behaviour, Online behaviour, Interest in a product, Social media account, User ID, Order history, Billing address Legitimate interestsLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:      Commercial interestsStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
WebsitePurpose:                      Website analyticsInformation:                Online behaviour, LocationLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:     Commercial interestsStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                      A/B testingInformation:                Online behaviour, LocationLegal basis:                 Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:     Commercial interestsStorage period:           As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                     AccountInformation:               Name, Email, Username, Password, User ID, Message contentLegal basis:                ConsentStorage period:           As long as necessary for this purpose
Purpose:                     Submitting reviews or messagesInformation:                Name, Email, Username, Password, User ID, Message contentLegal basis:                 ConsentStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purposeSecurity and fraud preventionPurpose:                      ID verificationInformation:                 IBAN number, Name, Address, Social security numberLegal basis:                  Legitimate interestsInterest concerned:      Commercial interestsStorage period:            As long as necessary for this purpose
How did we obtain your personal data?Conyplex B.V. has obtained your data because you have provided this data to us.What are your rights?Under the European General Data Protection Regulation you have a number of rights with regard to your data and the processing thereof:AccessYou may access your personal information and make any necessary changes in your account. If you would like to see which personal data Conyplex B.V. has obtained about you, you may exercise your right of access by submitting a request to Conyplex B.V..Making changesIf you wish to make changes to the personal information that you have seen as a result of a request for access and you are unable to make the changes yourself in your account, you may request that Conyplex B.V. makes these changes for you. You may request that Conyplex B.V. modifies, corrects, supplements, erases or shields your information.Restriction of processing of personal dataYou also have the right, under certain conditions, to ask Conyplex B.V. to restrict the processing of your personal data.Right to objectIf processing of your data takes place on the grounds of 'legitimate interest' by Conyplex B.V. or a third party, you have the right to object to that processing.Portability of dataYou have the right to obtain your personal data from Conyplex B.V.. Conyplex B.V. will provide this in a structured and commonly used format, which can easily be opened using commonly used digital systems.Withdrawing consentWhen the legal basis for a particular processing is your explicit consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent. This does not affect past processing, but does mean that we will no longer be allowed to process this data in the future. It may also result in Conyplex B.V. no longer being able to provide you with certain services.
Response from Conyplex B.V.A request can be sent to privacy@contestyachts.com. Conyplex B.V. will comply with your request as soon as possible and in any case no later than one (1) month after Conyplex B.V. has received such a request. If Conyplex B.V. rejects your request, we will indicate in our reply why the request was rejected.Recipients of your personal dataYour data may be transmitted to:·         Data processors·         Parties that are involved in the execution or fulfilment of an agreement between you and Conyplex B.V.·         External consultants
It is possible that Conyplex B.V. is required to submit your data to a third party, for example to fulfil a legal obligation.
Transfer to third countries or international organizationsIt may be necessary, for instance for technical and operational reasons, to transfer your (personal) data to affiliates of Conyplex B.V. located outside the European Economic Area. Due to the possibility that the regulations in the area of privacy protection do not offer the same protection as within the European Economic Area, Conyplex B.V. will use the Privacy Shield or the EU Model Clauses to protect your privacy as much as possible. If that is not possible, Conyplex B.V. will ask your consent to transfer your (personal) data to countries that do not maintain an adequate protection level. You may withdraw your consent at any time.
What are cookies and how does Conyplex B.V. use them?Cookies are small pieces of (text) information that are sent to your browser when you visit the website of Conyplex B.V. and then stored on the hard disk or in the memory of your device. The cookies placed via Conyplex B.V.'s website cannot damage your device or the files stored on it. With 'cookies', we also mean comparable techniques collecting information, such as device fingerprinting.
Can changes be made to this Privacy Statement?This Privacy Statement is subject to changes. We therefore advise you to regularly read the Privacy Statement for any such changes.
Questions, remarks, and complaintsIf you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the way in which Conyplex B.V. uses your data, you can send an e-mail to privacy@contestyachts.com. If you have a complaint about the way your data is processed, please send an e-mail to privacy@contestyachts.com. Furthermore, you always have the right to contact the competent national data protection authority. In The Netherlands, this is the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens
Contest Range
Sailing Yachts
Contest 42CS
Contest 45CS
Contest 50CS
Contest 55CS
Contest 59CS
Contest 62CS
